CHARLIE CHRISTIAN DEMIAR

VIRTUAL ASSISTANT



+639097497402

charliedemiar@gmail.com

Proper B, Brgy VF Gustilo, Cadiz City, Negros Occidental, Ph.

PROFILE

I've been working in a BPO industry as a customer service representative since 2016 in which I develop so much skills especially in decision making, providing excellent customer service and technical support is the most fulfilling part of this job, the love for learning is one the key reason why I'm transitioning to become a Virtual Assistant or being a freelancer.

SKILLS

- Project Management Tools
- Data Entry
- Social Media Management
- Design Thinking
- · Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

Panasiatic Solutions

2016 - 2022

- Corporate Escalation Personnel
- Technical Issue and Elderly People Support
- Sales Support

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

TTech Philippines 2022-present

- Billing Support
- Subject Matter Expert
- Community Expert

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Sewahon National High School 2010 - 2014

COLLEGE

Universal School of Applied Technology

2014 - 2016